[{"answer": "There's definitely more stories to be reported.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 7, "question": "What information does he have to reveal?", "qSentId": 6}, {"answer": "Well, I had a health crisis that led me to the cannabis industry.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 26, "question": "Cheryl, why was it important for you to start the Beverly Hills Cannabis Club and become known as the Martha Stewart of marijuana?", "qSentId": 25}, {"answer": "Well, in 1996, when Prop 215 was just passed in Los Angeles, my therapist, who, at that time, had me on anti-depressants and anxiety pills and sleeping pills, he actually suggested it to me.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "How has that happened?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "Did it change her as a person?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "I really find it frightening because there's really a lot of ignorance that is going on here.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 67, "question": "Dr. Samuels, as a recovering addict, what is your reaction to the pop moms?", "qSentId": 66}, {"answer": "I -- I disagree.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "You disagree?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "So, Doctor, why don't you think pot should be legalized?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "As a mother here's what I find very interesting.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "Ladies, what are -- what are your thoughts?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "No, not only is it a gateway drug, because if you were really in the field that I am, people are using marijuana at 14 years old because of people like this I'm debating.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "So there's -- no doubt to you, there's no doubt to you that marijuana is a gateway drug?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I loved CBD.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "What's the benefit of a place like that?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "The only benefit is with people with serious, you know, cancer issues and some pain issues.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "Any benefit to a place like Harborside?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "Doing well.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "Glenn, how are you?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "Every single time government officials try and do things and hide it from the American people and then get caught doing what they're doing, they do the same thing, they scream the word terrorism over and over in the hope that people will get scared.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "What is your reaction to what Director Keith Alexander said?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "I don't think so.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "If he was really a hero, wouldn't he have just, you know, be seen a little differently if he had just stuck around and kind of stood his ground?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "Well, you know, Barbara Starr is very good at going to government officials and having them whisper in her ear and then repeating what they say and calling that reporting.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "Why is that?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "Well, it isn't that he has more to reveal.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "What more information does he have to reveal?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "I think his -- his really -- his only goal is to make sure that he can continue to participate in the debate over surveillance, that was his main goal to help provoke.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "Do you know where he would like to go, what his preference is?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "Well, like I said, his -- as far as I know, he never -- even before he got to Russia, he doesn't have any intention of disclosing more information.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "What can you tell me about that?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "Well, there are ways to get from Moscow to Latin America without having to fly over airspace that is controlled by the United States or its allies.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "How difficult is it going to be for him, as he's working with the governments, trying to figure out a way to seek asylum, to create a travel plan since ultimately he is going to be flying through restricted airspace?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "I don't think he had any relationship with WikiLeaks, not -- at least not to my knowledge until WikiLeaks provided him with assistance in leaving Hong Kong at the request of the -- or at the invitation or with the permission of the government of Hong Kong and then seeking asylum.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "Does he continue to be in contact with the organization and Julian Assange?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "It's amazing.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "Do Snowden have any regrets giving up his life here in the United States?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "I'm doing fine.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "Congressman, how are you?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "You know, I've done a lot of work that's worse than picking oranges.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "Have you ever worked as a migrant farm worker, Congressman?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "I think there are 100 million Americans that are of working age that are simply not in the workforce.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "Do you think Americans are lining up for jobs like this?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's because just as I've said, that the magnet that keeps people there and in their homes is a large cradle-to-grave welfare system.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "Why do you think that is?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "Well, I read through the bill, and I look at what they're trying to do.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "When you look at this immigration reform, what's being proposed at the moment, can you tell me about your thoughts on the whole gang of eight immigration reform bill?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "Of course I do.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "Do you stand by these statements, Congressman?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "But here's the point.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "Should those people not have a chance to try and stay in our country?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "I have supported some of that STEM policy that's there, in two different times.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "Shouldn't we be giving them visas to stay in America?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "Well, I think that when you do this incrementally, you start moving people into the workforce that aren't there now.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "How will that affect all of us?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "Hey, man, thank you.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "Should it be that easy for someone to get a gun?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "Well, we have to collaborate and work together.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "What, in your opinion, could be done to change the gun culture there?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "Well, whenever you have so much economic deprivation in a certain area, you have educational problems, economic problems, social ills with the breakdown in the structure of family and then you add to that the lack of any spirituality, and you have all of that in one neighborhood, it's going to breed a lot of hopelessness, a lot of frustration.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "Why is that?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "Well, you know, compared to the rest of America, they're -- they're pretty strict.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "How strict are the gun laws in Chicago?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "ROOKS: We do have an influx of guns in the city.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "Does that lead to an influx of guns in the city?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "You know, here in Chicago, we have to start -- and not just Chicago, but, inner cities across America, whether it's New York, Philadelphia, Los Angeles, inner cities across America.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 488, "question": "What does this say, that there are these kind of children shooting children problems?", "qSentId": 487}, {"answer": "I think, oftentimes, there are a lot of people who -- who may deem that black-on-black crime or young black boys killing young black boys is not as newsworthy, for one.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "Why do you think that is?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "She started coming when I first opened the shop 41 years ago.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "(on camera): Peggy (ph), how long has Tootie been coming here?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "(INAUDIBLE), Tootie?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "Five o'clock.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "Tootie, what time did you wake up?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "Yes, I just do what I want to do.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "So, Tootie, do you do anything to get any exercise?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "I'm grateful I can.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "You still get around pretty good?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130727pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "(on camera): Keep stirring this, right?", "qSentId": 540}]